打起精神来　泰德
Pull yourself together Teddy!
镇定
Pull yourself together!
只是水而已
It's just water.
很多的水
It's a lot of water.
振作点
Come on.
-你没事吧　老大　 -我没事
- You okay boss? - Yeah, I'm fine. I just... I just can't
我只是晕船
I just can't stomach the water.
-你是我的新搭档?　 -没错
- So you're my new partner? - That's right.
我刚才在厕所里吐完一轮 真不是见面的好时机啊
Not the best way to meet with my head halfway down the toilet.
你和我听说的泰德　丹尼尔的传说不一样
Doesn't exactly square with Teddy Daniels: The man. The legend. I'll give you that.
传说?
The Legend?
你们在波特兰又乱编了什么传奇?
What the hell are you boys smoking out there in Portland anyway?
是西雅图
Seattle.
我来自西雅图分部的
I came from the office in Seattle.
你做联邦警察多长时间了
How long have you been with Marshals?
4年
Four years.
那你知道这官有多么小
- So you know how small it is? - Sure
你呢　有女友吗　结婚了吗
What about you? You got a girl? Married?
我曾有
I was.
她死了
She died.
-对不起　我不知道...　 -没事
- Jesus... I didn't... - Don't worry about it.
我们家的公寓楼失火了　当时我在工作
There was a fire at the apartment building while I was at work
死了四个人
Four People died.
她不是被烧死的而是被浓烟熏死的
It was the smoke that got her not the fire. So...
-这一点很重要　 -真不幸
- So that's important. - I'm sorry Boss.
我的烟呢?
Where are my goddamn cigarettes?
来抽我的吧
Well here. Have one of mine.
我记得是放在我的外套里了
I could of sworn they were in my jacket when I got on.
为政府工作就是没有什么油水
Government employees will rob you blind.
谢谢
Thanks.
你来以前知道这个机构的情况吗
They give you a briefing about the institution before you left?
我只知道这是家精神病院
All I know is it's a mental hospital.
里头关着精神病罪犯
For the criminally insane.
如果只是有幻觉的
Well, if it was just folks running around, hearing voices,
或者疯疯癫癫的精神病　就不用我们出马了
and chasing after butterflies, they wouldn't need us.
我们就到那里?　对
- That's where we're headed? - Yup.
岛的四面是悬崖
The other side of the island is rock bluffs
悬崖下面紧靠着海
all the way down to the edge of the water.
码头是进出唯一的路
The dock, it's the only way on...or off.
你们一上岸我们就开船离开
We will be casting off as soon as you two are ashore.
希望你们能动作快点
I'd appreciate if you'd hurry up about it.
-为什么　 -暴风雨要来了
- Why? - Storm's coming.
我从没见过联邦警察的徽章
I've never seen a marshal's badge before.
我是副典狱长麦克弗森,你们好
I'm Deputy Warden McPherson, gentlemen.
欢迎来到隔离岛　 我带你们去管理中心
Welcome to Shutter Island. I'll be the one taking you up to Ashecliffe.
你的手下好像如临大敌似的紧张的很
Your boys seem a little on edge Mr. McPherson.
现在这情况下　我们都这样
Right now, Marshal. We all are.
记住我们也曾活过　爱过　笑过
"Remember us for we too have lived, loved and laughed"
篱笆都通了电
Electrified perimeter.
你怎么看出来的
How could you tell?
我以前见过这种装置
I've seen something like it before.
好了　我们会给予你们尽可能的帮助
All right. You gentlemen will be accorded all the help we can give.
但是在岛上期间　你们要遵守规定　明白吗
But during the stay you will obey protocol. Is that understood?
当然
Absolutely.
右边的红砖建筑是A栋病房　男性病房
The red brick bulding on my right is ward A, the male ward.
B栋病房是女性病房　就是左边这栋
Ward B, the female ward, is the one on the left.
C栋病房是悬崖上的这栋建筑
Ward C is that building on the bluffs. An old civil war fort.
里面是最危险的病人
The most dangerous patients are housed there.
要进入C栋病房　必须有书面批准
Admittance to ward C is forbidden without the written consent and
以及我本人和考利医生的陪同
physical presence of both myself and Dr. Cawly.
明白吗
Is that understood?
看来你也被精神病传染了
You act like insanity is catching.
你们要交出武器
You are hereby required to surrending your firearms.
麦克弗森先生　我们都是正式任命的联邦警察
Mr. McPherson, we are duly appointed federal marshals.
我们必须随时带着武器
We are required to carry our firearms with us at all times.
关于监狱的联邦法令319条规定
Executive order 319 of the Federal Code of Penitentiaries states that:
在监狱内部
when inside the penitentiary
监狱长拥有最高权威
the offices of that institution have final authority.
先生们　你们交出武器才能进这个门
Gentlemen, you will not get through this gate with your firearms.
例行程序就到这里　来吧
Okay. Now that the official stuff is done, come on boys.
我们去找考利医生吧
What do you say we go find Dr. Cawley?
她是怎么逃走的　那个犯人?
So when did she escape? This prisoner?
这些情况考利医生会向你介绍
I'm afraid that Dr. Cawley will have to fill you in on the situation.
这是规定
Protocol.
精神病院里也有狱警
Correctional officers at a mental institution.
看起来挺奇怪啊
That's a weird sight, if you don't mind me saying
这在美国是独一无二的
It's the only facility of it's kind in the U.S. Even in the world.
在世界上也是　我们只收留最危险的精神病人
We take only the most dangerous, damaged patients.
都是别的精神病院管不了的　这都多亏了考利医生
Ones no other hospital can manage. And it's all due to Dr. Cawley.
他创立了独特的管理方武
He's created something really unique here. It's a hospital for people our society normally...
身份验证　先生们
ID's, gentlemen.
请出示警徽
Show your badges, gentlemen.
考利医生接受过多次咨询
Dr. Cawley's been consulted numerous times
伦敦警察厅　军情五处　战略情报局　为什么
- By Scotland Yard, MI5, the OSS... - Why?
你什么意思
What do you mean?
情报机构为什么要咨询精神病学家?
What do intelligence agencies want to consult a psychatrist about?
这你要问他了
I guess you'll have to ask him.
丹尼尔联邦警察　医生
- Marshal Daniels. - Doctor.
我是奥尔联邦警察
Marshal Aule.
谢谢你副典狱长　可以了　是
- Thank you deputy warden, that will be all. - Yes, sir.
很荣幸先生们
Pleasure, gentlemen.
他提到你很多次
He had a lot to say about you.
麦克弗森是个好人　他相信我们在这里的工作
McPherson is a good man. He believes in the work we do here.
那么到底是什么工作
And what would that be exactly?
法律、秩序和医疗的结合
A moral fusion between law and order and clinical care.
什么和什么
Pardon me Doc... a what between what and what?
这些画画得很准确
Those paintings are quite accurate.
这就是我们以前对付的那种病人
It used to be that the kind of patients we deal with here
戴上镰铐　不管不问
were shackled and left in their own filth.
经常被打得浑身是血
They were beaten. As if whipping them bloody would drive the psychosis out.
把螺丝钉钉入其头部　按到水里直至昏迷
We drove screws into their brains. We submerged them in icy water until they lost consciousness.
甚至淹死
Or even drown.
现在呢?　我们治疗他们
- And now? - We treat them.
尽量让他们治愈
Try to heal, try to cure.
即使不奏效　也会给他们的生活带来信心　带来心情的平静
And if this fails, at least we provide them with a measure of comfort in their lives. Calm.
这里的都是...
These are...
暴力罪犯吧
all violent offenders, right?
伤害过人
They've hurt people.
甚至有的杀过人　基本都是杀过人的
- Murdered them in some cases. - In almost all cases. Yes.
我个人看来这种人就不用给他们平静感了
Then personally Doctor, I'd have to say... screw their sense of calm.
我职责是治疗病人 不是治疗受害人 我对他们没有偏见
It's my job to treat my patients not their victims. I'm not here to judge.
那么女性犯人中...　病人
- So this female prisoner... - Patient.
对不起　女性病人中瑞秋索兰多
Excuse me, patient. One Rachel Solando,
昨晚刚逃走了
- Escaped sometime in the last 24 hours.
10点到12点之间
Last night, between 10 and midnight.
她可说是个很危险的人
- Is she considered dangerous? - You could say that.
她杀了她的三个孩子
She killed all three of her children.
在她家后面的湖里淹死了他们
She drowned them in the lake behind her house.
把他们一个一个的按进水中　直到淹死
She took them out one by one and held their heads under until they died.
然后再把他们抱回到餐桌旁
Then she brought them back inside and arranged them around the kitchen table.
邻居来拜访的时候　她正在吃饭呢
She ate a meal there before a neighbor dropped by.
她丈夫呢
And what about the husband?
死于诺曼底登陆　她是战争遗族
He died. On the beaches of Normandy. She is a war widow.
刚来的时候绝食 坚持说孩子没有死
She starved herself when first she came here. She insisted the children weren't dead.
对不起　医生　你有阿司匹林吗　 头疼吗　警官?
- Sorry doctor. You wouldn't happen to have an aspirin? Do you? - Prone to headaches marshal.
有时会 不过今天
Sometimes, but today...
是因为晕船　啊　脱水了
- I'm a little more prone to seasickness. - Ah, Dehydration...
没事吧老大　没事
- You alright boss? - Yes.
对付这种情况　越简单的办法越好
In that case you're quite right. The simpler the better.
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
瑞秋仍然相信孩子还活着
Rachel still believes her children are alive.
她还认为这里就是她在伯克郡的家
She also believes this place is her home in the Berckshires.
不会吧
You're kidding me.
在这家精神病院的四年中
She's never once in two years acknowledged that she is in an institution.
她认为我们都是...
She believes we're all...
送货员　快递小弟　邮差
deliveryman, milkman, postal workers.
为了保持孩子还活着的错觉 她还创造了复杂的虚构场景
To sustain the illusion that her children never died, she's created an elaborate fictional structure.
我们都成了她虚构场景的角色
She gives us all parts to play in that fiction.
你们搜查过了吗　典狱长带人搜遍了岛上
- So have you searched the grounds yet? - The warden and his men scoured the island,
没有线索
not a trace.
更令人不安的是　我们不知道她是怎么离开房间的
What's more disturbing is, we don't know how she got out of her room.
房间是由外面锁上的
It was locked from the outside
唯一的窗户也有铁栅栏
and the only window is barred.
好像她穿过墙蒸发了
It's as if she evaporated straight through the walls.
在群体治疗后把她带回来　锁在房间里
Brought her right back here after group therapy, locked her in
午夜查房的时候　就发现她不见了
I came back for a midnight round and she was gone.
说真的　医生　她怎么会一直没有发现事实呢
Seriously doctor, how is it possible that the truth never gets through to her?
没发现自己是个精神病?
I mean, she's in a mental institution, right?
她总该发现有哪里不正常
Seems like something you'd notice from time to time.
-每个病人都有几双鞋?　 -两双
- How many pairs of shoes are the patients given? - Two pairs.
不是人人都可以神智健全的
Sanity is not a choice, marshal,
不能想克服就克服
You can't just choose to get over it.
那么　她光着脚走了?
So... she left here barefoot?
外面地形崎岖　光着脚走不了多远
Come on Doc, she couldn't get ten yards in that terrain.
警官?!
Marshal?
这肯定是瑞秋的笔迹
Well this is definitely Rachel's handwriting.
-我不知道第四条定律是什么意思 -不是精神病学术语?
- I have no idea what the "law of 4" is, though. - It's not a psychiatric term?
应该不是
I'm afraid not.
谁是67号？
Who's 67?
我不知道
Fuck if I know!
我觉得还是临床病理派 比较会解释
I'd have to say that's quite close to my clinical conclusion.
那么你觉得这只是随便乱写的?
So you think it's random scribblings?
不是的　瑞秋很聪明　非常聪明
Oh no, not at all. Rachel is smart. Brilliant in fact.
-这张纸可能很重要　 -对不起　医生
- This paper could be important. - Excuse me Doctor, but...
-我们要留着它　 -那当然
- We're gonna have to hold onto this. - Of course.
逃走的话必须经过这里
And you say she had to come through here.
熄灯后　勤务人员就在这里打牌打整夜
After lights out, the orderlies play cards in here.
昨晚有7个人坐在楼梯下面玩牌
Last night there were 7 men sitting at the base of those stairs playing stud poker.
但是瑞秋却从他们身边溜过去了
Yet somehow, Rachel managed to slip past them.
为什么
Why?
怎么溜过去的? 隐形了?
How? She turns invisible?
医生　我们需要所有医务人员的个人档案
Doctor, we're gonna need access to personnel files of all the medical staff.
还有护士　警卫和勤务人员
The nurses, the guards, the orderlies.
在这里工作的所有人　 我们会考虑你所提的申请
- Anyone who was working then. - We'll take your request under consideration.
这不是申请，医生
This is not a request, Doctor.
这是联邦机构 如今一位危险的犯人...
This is a federal facility and a dangerous prisoner...
病患　病患
- Patient. - Patient...
已经逃走了 你必须照我说的, 否则.. 我只能说，我会尽量帮忙
- has escaped now. You will comply... - All I can say is that I will see what I can do.
医生　我们需要和工作人员谈一谈　你明白吗？
Doctor, we're gonna need to speak with the staff, do you understand?
我会在饭后让他们到休息室集合
I'll assemble them in the common room after dinner.
如果你还有别的问题　可以加入副典狱长的搜索行动
If you have any further questions feel free to join the deputy warden in the search.
离这岛最近的陆地也有11英里　水又这么冷
It's 11 miles to the nearest land and the water is freezing.
昨晚浪很大
The current was strong last night. The tide pushing in.
她会淹死　或者被浪冲到岩石上撞死 尸体会冲到海岸上
She'd have drowned or been crushed on the rocks, and her body would have washed back up onshore.
搜查过那边的山洞了吗
What about those caves down there, have you checked them?
她不可能在里面
No way she could get there.
悬崖下面都是毒藤　槲树、漆树
The base of those cliffs are covered in poison ivy, live oak, sumac
很多植物的荆棘比我的手指还要长
and a thousand plants with thorns as big as my dick.
你也看到了　她连个鞋子都没有.
You said it yourself marshal, she's got no shoes.
好了我们去找另一边
All right! Let's check the other side!
那栋是什么? 以前是个灯塔
- What's that tower? - It's an old lighthouse.
警卫已经找过那了
The guards already searched inside it.
里面有什么? 关别的病人?　 -污水处理设施
- What's in there? More patients? - Sewage treatment facility.
快天黑了
It's getting dark soon.
今天就到这里吧
I'm calling this off for the night.
我们走吧
Let's go, boys!
当时是你执勤?　对
- You were on watch on the landing, huh? - Yeah.
有人经过走廊 我不可能看不见
Can't nobody get in or out of their room in that corridor without me seeing.
好的 瑞秋索兰多
Okay, Rachel Solando,
她要到这里 还需要经过谁
who else does she have to pass to get down here?
我
Me.
格兰米亚
Glen Miga.
长官　我什么都没看见　 你一晚上都没离开?
- Sir, I didn't see nothing. - And you were at your post all night?
是的　但我什么都没看见
Yes. But I didn't see a thing.
格兰
Glen.
对我说实话
Tell me the truth.
我可能去过一趟洗手间
I maybe... went to the bathroom.
什么? 你违反了规则? 天啊　我只离开了一分钟吧
- What? You breached protocol? Christ... - I wasn't gone more than a minute.
我们再回顾一遍
All right, let's back up here. Let's all just back up.
熄灯之前把瑞秋 带回房间
Miss Solando was put in her room for lights out.
谁知道她回到房间之前还做了什么
Does anybody here know  what she did before that?
谁知道
Anyone?
有没有人知道
Come on. Anyone. Anyone. Anyone.
她参加了群体治疗
She was in a group therapy session.
那他有没有什么异常?
Huh. Did anything unusual occur?
异常怎么定义？
Define "unusual".
你说什么　这可是精神病院　警官?!
- Excuse me. - It's a mental institution, marshal.
这里关着一群精神病罪犯
For criminally insane.
所谓的正常反而很难碰到
"Usual", isn't a big part of our day.
那我换个说法
I will rephrase.
在昨天晚上的群体治疗期间
Did anything happen last night during group therapy, that was more...
有没有比平时更...　引人注意的?
- let's say, more memorable than... - Normal?
没错
Exactly!
没有　对不起
No. I'm sorry.
群体治疗的时候　瑞秋说过什么吗
Did Mrs. Solando say anything during group therapy?
她担心暴风雨
She was worried about the rain.
还讨厌这里的伙食
And she hated the food here.
经常抱怨　昨晚也是
Complained constantly. Last night included.
当时有没有医生在场?
So... you were there. Was there a doctor present?
是的　希恩医生主持
Yes. Dr. Sheehan led the discussion.
希恩医生?
Dr. Sheehan?
是的　他主持的治疗
Yes. He was running the session.
他是瑞秋的主治医生
He's Rachels's "primary".
直接负责她的治疗
The psychaiatrist who directly oversees her care.
我们需要和希恩医生谈谈
We're gonna need to speak with Dr. Sheehan.
这是不可能的
I'm afraid that won't be possible.
他今早坐船离开码头了　他的休假早已安排好了
He left on the ferry this morning. His vacation was already planned.
结果一直被延后放不了假
He'd putting it off too long.
你们这是一级管制区
You're in a state of lockdown.
一个危险的病人逃走了
A dangerous patient has escaped
你们却让他的主治医生休假去了?
and you let her primary doctor leave on vacation?
那当然，他又不是病人
Of course, he's a doctor.
你有他的联络电话吗？
Do you have the phone number for where he's gone?
喂　喂
Hello? Hello?
喂
Hello?
有人在吗
Is anybody there?
对不起　长官　所有线路都不通
I'm sorry sir, but its all down. All the lines.
线路大概都被暴风雨破坏了
The storm's hitting the mainland like a hammer.
如果能接通　立刻告诉我　 警官 有很重要的电话要打
If you get it working, come find me immediately. The marshalls need to make an important call.
是
Yes, sir.
我晚上还要到病房巡视
I'm afraid I have evening rounds in the wards,
不过9点左右　我会在家里喝酒抽烟
But I'll be having drinks and a cigar at my house around 9
你可以来玩
If you'd care to drop by
好　到那时就可以谈了吧
Good, we can talk then, right?
我们一直在谈　警官
We have been talking, marshal.
这里真不像精神病院应有的设施
Gotta say, I'm thinking I got into the wrong line of public service.
确实有点太过豪华　这是内战时盖的
It is a little overwhelming. it was constructed during the Civil War
军事堡垒也是同时盖好的　也就是现在的C栋病房
The same time as the military fort housing ward C.
这里曾经是指挥总部　花了美国政府一大笔钱
This is the original commander's quarters. When Uncle Sam got the bill
盖好不久，指挥官就被送上军事法庭
the commander was court-martialed.
看得出来..
I can see why.
音乐不错　勃拉姆斯的曲子?
Nice music. Who is that? Brahms?
不是
No.
是马勒的作品
It's Mahler.
正确,警官
Quite right, marshal.
对不起　先生们　这是我的同事杰里米纳林医生
Forgive me, gentlemen... My colleague, Dr. Jeremiah Naehring.
钢琴乐与弦乐四重奏A小调
"Quartet for Piano and Strings in A minor"
你们喝什么　裸麦威士忌　如果有的话
- Your poison, gentlemen? - Rye, if you've got it.
冰镇汽水　谢谢
Soda and ice please, thanks.
你不喜欢喝酒?
You don't indulge in alcohol?
真是没想到
I am surprised.
你这种职业的人不都是挺能喝吗
Isn't it common for men in your profession to imbibe?
差不多　你这种职业的人呢
Common enough. And yours?
你说什么？　你的职业―精神科医生
- I'm sorry? - Your profession, doctor. Psychiatry...
我听说精神科医生都是一群酒鬼
I've always heard it was overrun with boozers and drunks.
我倒是没发现
Not that I've noticed.
难道你喝的是红茶吗
What's that? Iced tea in your glass there?
好样的　警官
Excellent marshal.
你很擅于自我防卫
You have outstanding defense mechanisms.
你肯定很擅长拷问
You must be quite adept at interrogations, hmm?
你们这样的人　就是我的研究对像
Men like you... are my specialty. You know?
暴力之人
Men of violence.
这假设有点问题
That's a hell of an assumption to make...
不是假设　你误会了　我说你们是暴力的人
No assumption. Not at all. You misunderstand me, I said you are men of violence
不是说你们是使用暴力的人　这大不一样
I'm not accusing you of being violent men. That's quite different.
请讲解一下吧　医生
Please, please, edify us, doctor.
你们都曾在海外服役
You both served overseas.
时间不长　医生　我们在国外不是作文职工作
Not much of a stretch, Doc. For all you know, we were both paper pushers over there
嗯 你们不是
No, you were not.
我肯定你们从毕业后 就一直再打仗
Since the schoolyard, neither of you has ever walked away from a physical conflict.
并不是说你们喜欢打仗 只是因为你们没法接受撤
Not because you enjoy it, but because retreat wasn't something you considered an option.
政府养我们不是为了逃跑的
We weren't raised to run, Doc.
是啊　养你们
Ah, yes... Raised.
谁养了你　警官？
and who raised you, marshal?
我吗?
Me?
狼
Wolves.
厉害的自我防卫
Very impressive defense mechanisms.
你相信上帝吗? 警官
Do you believe in God, marshal?
我是认真的
I'm quite serious.
你这是废话
That's rubbish.
你见过纳粹集中营吗
Have you ever seen... a death camp, doctor?
我在解放达豪集中营的时候见过
[In German] I have, I was there, for the liberation of Dakau.
你的英语说得很好
Your English is very good, almost flawless.
说得很好　不过辅音发的有点重
His English is very good. You hit the consonants a tad hard, though.
你是德国人?
You're German?
合法移民也是犯罪吗,警官? 　 我不知道　你最清楚
- Is legal immigration a crime, marshal? - Oh I don't know doctor, you to tell us.
听着我们需要希恩医生的档案　还有其它员工的
Now listen, we're gonne need those files on Sheehan and the rest of staff as well.
员工的档案是绝对不会给你的　 -免谈
No personnel files will be released for you. Period.
我们需要档案　 -办不到
- We're gonna need those files. - Out of the question.
什么不可能　胡扯
Bullshit, out of the question! Bullshit!
这里谁说了算
Who the hell is in charge here anyway, huh?
纳林医生是我们海外董事会的联络人
Dr. Naehring acts as liaison to our board of overseers.
他已提交你的请求　但被拒绝了
He relayed your request and it's been refused.
拒绝? 他们无权拒绝　你也没有
Refused? They don't have the authority to refuse. And neither do you, sir.
警官先生　请继续你的调查　我们会尽全力协助
Marshal, continue your investigation and we will do all we can to help.
调查结束了!
This investigation is over.
我们要把调查报告交给...
We're gonna file our reports and hand it over to...
-联邦调查局　 -联邦调查局　没错!
- Hoover's boys. - Hoover's boys, that's right.
我们明早就搭船走
We'll be taking the ferry back in the morning.
走吧　查克
Come on, Chuck.
夜色不错
Nice night.
你们在勤务人员区住宿
You'll be bunking in the orderlies quarter.
老大　我们真的要停止调查?
Hey boss?... We really packing it in?
为什么
Why?
我以前从没有中途放弃过
I guess, I dunno, I just... never really quit anything before.
我们到现在没听到一句实话　查克
We haven't heard the truth once yet, Chuck.
瑞秋不可能没人帮助　 就光着脚从锁着的房间里溜走
Listen. Rachel Solando did not slip out of a locked cell barefoot without any help.
她得到了很多的帮助
I think she had alot of help.
也许考利现在正坐在豪宅里
Maybe Cawley's sitting up in his mansion right now,
思考他今晚的态度
rethinking his whole attitude.
-或许到明早...　 -你是虚张声势?
- Maybe in the morning... - You're bluffing?
我没这么说
I didn't say that.
我发现很多这种酒　泰德
I found a whole stack of these, Teddy.
你是不是一天喝到晚
Jesus, are you ever sober anymore?
我在战争中杀死很多人
I killed alot of people in the war.
所以你就喝酒?
Is that why you drink?
你是讲真的吗
Are you real?
不是
No.
她还在这里
She's still here.
谁
Who?
瑞秋?
Rachel?
她从未离开
She never left.
记得我们在湖边的小屋吗
Remember when we stayed in the cabin in the summer, Teddy?
当时那么幸福
We were so happy.
她在这里
She's here.
你不能走
You can't leave.
我不会走的
I'm not gonna leave.
我如此爱你
I love you so much.
我现在已经是棺材里的骨灰了　泰德　不
- I'm just bones in a box, Teddy. - No.
是的
I am.
你必须清醒过来
You have to wake up.
我不会走的
I won't go.
你在这里
You're here.
我没有
I'm not.
你必须面对现实
You have to face that.
但她在这里
But she is.
他也是
And so is he.
谁
Who?
雷德斯
Laeddis.
我必须走了
I have to go.
请不要走
No! Please...just let me hold you.
再留一会　泰德
- Just a little bit longer. - Oh, Teddy...
你必须让我走
You have to let me go.
我不能
I can't.
这样的天气船不会来了
Ain't gonna be no ferry in this shit.
医生
Doctor.
Doctor, doctor.
我们要讯问 和瑞秋一同参加群体治疗的病人
We need to interview the patients who were in Rachel's group therapy session.
你的调查不是结束了吗
I thought your investigation was finished?
这种天气会有船来吗？
It's not like we can take the ferry.
瑞秋有没有接受其它的治疗?
Now was Rachel receiving any other treatment for her illnesses?
你了解当今的精神治疗学派吗
Do you know the state of the mental health field these days, gentlemen?
完全不知道　医生
No. Not a clue doctor.
是个战争
War.
传统观点认为需要外科手术
The old school believes in surgical intervention.
精神外科学　切除前脑叶白质
Psychosurgery. Procedures like the trans-orbital lobotomy.
有人认为病人变得更理性了 有人认为病人变的像僵尸了
Some say the patients become reasonable, docile. Others say they become zombies.
现代观点呢　精神药理学
- And the new school? - Psycho pharmacology.
一种新型药物已经被批准
A new drug has just been  approved called Thorazine.
可以让精神病人放松
Which relaxes psychotic patients.
或者说驯服
You could say it tames them.
那么你是哪种观点呢　医生　我?
- And which school are you in, Doc? - Me?
我有一种激进的观点：就是尊重病人
I have this radical idea that if you treat a patient with respect,
倾听他们说话
listen to him,
尽力理解　就能懂得病人
try and understand, you just might reach him.
这些病人　实时这种病人也可以
- These patients? - Even these.
本来是最后一招　却成为第一疗法
What should be a last resort is becoming a first response.
给病人吃药　让他待上一会　病情就会减轻
Give them a pill, put them in a corner, and it all goes away.
瑞秋以前服用几种药物
Rachel Solando was on a combination of drugs
来控制暴力的发作　但效果只有间歇性的
meant to keep her from becoming violent, but it was only intermittently effective.
从以前，她康复的最大障碍就是拒绝面对她曾经的罪行
The greatest obstacle to her recovery was her refusal to face what she had done.
"以前"？
"Was."
你这么说　是知道她已经死了吗
Is there a reason you keep referring to your patient in the past tense, doctor?
看外面是什么天气吧
Look outside, marshal.
她还能活着吗
Why do you think?
下一个是彼得布尔　用药罐的玻璃碎片割伤他爸爸看护
Next up is Peter Breen. Assaulted his father's nurse with a broken glass.
护士没死　但却终身毁容了
Nurse survived, but her face permaanently disfigured.
真想见见这个人
I can't wait.
她常对我笑　很客气
She'd smiles at me. She was so sweet.
但是从她的眼睛里能看出来　她喜欢裸体
But... I could see it in her eyes. She liked to be naked.
喜欢性爱
To suck cock.
好了　布尔先生
Okay, Mr. Breen.
她和我单独在厨房里
And then she asked me if she can have a glass of water?
对我轻松的说，帮我倒杯水
Alone in the kitchen? Like that's no big deal?
-喝杯水怎么了　 -他这样的隐喻还不明显吗？
- Why was that a big deal? - It was obvious.
她就是为了让我脱下裤子　 嘲笑我的家伙多么小
She wanted me to pull out my thing so she could laugh at it.
布尔先生
Mr. Breen,
我们需要问你一些问题
we need to ask you some questions, okay?
我一边划　她一边叫
When I cut her she screamed
不过
But...
她怕我
She scared me.
我当然要让她怕我
What did she expect?
是吗
Interesting.
但我们是来问你有关瑞秋索兰多的事情
But we are here to talk Rachel Solando, okay?
瑞秋索兰多
Rachel Solando...
你知道她淹死了自己的孩子吗
Did you know she had drowned her own kids?
她淹死了自己的孩子
She drowned her kids!
真是个变态的世界
This is a sick fucking world we live in. I'll tell you that...
这种人应该被关到毒气室
You know what? They should be gassed.
也包括白痴杀人犯
All of them... the retards, the killers
还有黑人　杀死自己的孩子　这贱货就该被毒死
the niggers. You kill your own kid? Gas the bitch!
你能不能不要画了?
Would you... stop that?
-护士.. -停下来!
- A nurse? - Please. Stop that.
护士或许有孩子
A nurse maybe. Maybe she had kids, huh?
有丈夫
A husband...
只想赚点钱贴补家用
Just trying to make ends meet,
只想正常地过日子
to lead a normal life...
她照顾你父亲
And it says in your file that uh...
你却划破她的脸　是不是
You tore her face off, didn't you?
恭喜你　她再也过不了什么正常生活了
Congratulations, no more normal for her, not ever again, no.
你知道她害怕的是什么吗
Do you know what she was afraid of?
是你
You.
你能不能不要画了
Could you stop that, please?!
别画了!
Stop that!
别再画了!
Please... stop!
-你认识一个叫安德鲁雷德斯的病人吗？ -不认识
You know a patient by the name of Andrew Laeddis?
我想回去
- I want to go back. - Take him!
我永远不会出院的
I'll never get out of here.
我也不该出去
I'm not sure that I should.
有句话可能不合适
Excuse me for saying this,
-卡恩斯小姐　 -太太
- Miss Kearns... - Misses.
卡恩斯太太
Mrs. Kearns.
你看起来...
But you seem...
很正常
quite normal,...
和其它病人相比的话
I mean in comparison with the other patients here.
每个人都做过不光彩的事情
Well, I have my dark days I suppose everybody does.
只不过一般人不会拿斧头把自己老公砍死的
The difference is that most people don't kill their husbands with an axe.
尤其老公又他见过的一半女人上床
Although personally I think if a man beats you and fucks
跟很多女人鬼混的人　是没人会帮他的
half the women he sees and no one will help you,
拿斧头砍死他　是很容易理解的
axing him isn't the least understandable thing you can do.
或许你真不该出院
Maybe you shouldn't get out.
我出院又能干什么呢
And what would I do if I did?
我已经不了解当今世界了　据说现在有一种
I don't know the world anymore. They say there are
把整个城市夷为平地的炸弹
bombs that can reduce whole cities to ash
还有一种叫做电视的东西
And what do they call "televisions"...
人关在盒子里还有声音跟影像
voices and faces coming from a box.
我在这里早就听腻声音了
I hear enough voices already
你知道瑞秋的什么东西？
What can you tell us about Rachel?
了解不多　她很内向
Um. Not much, she... she keeps to herself.
她相信她的孩子还活着
She believed her kids were alive.
她以为仍然自己还住在伯克郡　 而我们都是她的邻居
She thought she was still living in the Berkshires and we were all neighbours
快递小弟　邮差...　送货员
- The milkman, postmen... - Deliveryman,
那晚希恩医生也在
And Dr. Sheehan was there that night?
是的
Yes. Um.
他讲解怎么控制发怒的情绪
He talked about anger.
说些有关他的事情..
Tell me about him...
他是什么样的人
What's he like?
他...
I think he's uh...
不错　还满好的
Okay... nice.
用我妈妈的话说　是那种目光和蔼的人
Not hard on the eyes as my mother would say.
他勾引过你吗
Did he ever make a pass at you?
没有
No.
希恩是个好医生　他不会做出...
No, Dr. Sheehan is a good doctor, he would never...
能给我倒杯水吗
Could I have a glass of water, please?
没问题
No problem.
谢谢你,警官
Thank you, marshal.
我还有一个问题 卡思斯太大
I have just one more question for you Mrs. Kearns.
你有没有见过叫安德鲁雷德斯的病人
Did you ever meet a patient named Andrew Laeddis?
没有
No.
没听说过
Never heard of him.
她的回答有人指点过
She was coached.
所有的话，跟考利和护士的回答如出一辙
She used practically the same words as Cawley and the nurse.
-让她说什么　她就说什么　 -安德鲁雷德斯是谁?
- Like she'd been told exactly what to say. - Who is Andrew Laeddis?
为何每个病人你都会问到这人？他是谁？
You asked every one of those patients back there about him. Who is he?
对我也要隐瞒? 我可是你的搭档
What the hell, boss, I'm your partner for the Christ's sake!
我们认识不久　查克
We just met, Chuck.
你一直是行政人员
You've been on the beat a long time.
有职责　有事业　而我做的
You got a duty, got a career. What I'm doing,
严格上来讲，并不是遵守法律规范的
is not exactly by the book.
我才不管什么法律勒　我只想知道是怎么回事
I don't give a damn about "by the book", boss I just to know what the hell is going on.
这件案子提报到单位的时候
When this case came over the wires,
-我主动要求要办里这件案子　你知道吗？ -为什么
- I requested it specifically. Do you understand? - Why?
安德鲁雷德斯
Andrew Laeddis,
是我和我老婆住的公寓里同栋的维修工
was the maintenance man in the apartment building where my wife and I lived.
然后呢？
Okay.
他是个纵火犯
He was also a firebug.
安德鲁雷德斯点着了火柴
Andrew Laeddis lit the match,
搞出了害死我妻子的火灾
that caused the fire that killed my wife.
锁上
Let 'em out!
雷德斯后来怎么样了
What happened to Laeddis?
逃离了追捕　然后就失踪了
Got away with it. Laeddis got away with it and disappeared.
大概一年前　我在份报纸上看到了他
About a year ago, I opened up the newspaper and there he is.
这丑陋的混蛋
He's an ugly looking son of a bitch.
有一道长长的伤疤　从右太阳穴一直划到左嘴唇
He had a new scar from his right temple down to his left lip.
眼球的颜色两边不一样　是一副让人印象深刻的面孔
Eyes different colors. Not the type of face you forget.
后来他烧毁一间学校　死了两个人
He'd burned down a schoolhouse. Killed 2 people.
说是奉了神的旨意
He said voices told him to do it.
先进了监狱　然后转移到这里
First he was sent to prison and then he was transferred here.
-后来呢？ -后来就没有消息了
- Then what? - Then, nothing.
他整个人就这样消失了　好像从未存在　没有任何记录
He vanished like he never existed. No record whatsoever.
他如果不在女性病房　那么肯定在C栋病房了
I'm sure he's not in ward B that leaves ward C.
搞不好他早死了
Or he could be dead.
瑞秋搞不好也死了　这里藏几具尸体还是很简单的
So could Rachel Solando for that matter. Lot of places to hide a body here.
只有一个地方没有人注意到
Only one place no one really knows.
那个卡恩斯太太　让我去倒水的时候
That patient, Bridget Kearne, when she sent me for water,
对你说过什么吧
she said something to you back there, didn't she?
没有
No.
得了吧　老大
Come on boss!
她用写的
She wrote it.
老大
Boss!
我们要到屋里去　暴风要演变成飓风了
We gotta get indoors. It's turning into fucking Kansas out here...
好　我们走吧
- All right. - Now. Let's go!
当心
Watch out!
天啊
Jesus!
快　我们回去
Come on! Let's go back!
天啊
Jesus Christ! Damn it!
你没事吧　我没事
- Are you okay boss? - Yes. That's all right.
雷德斯一定在这里
So... if Laeddis is here...
你打算怎么办呢 老大
What are you going to do boss?
我不是来杀雷德斯的
I'm not here to kill Leaddis.
如果他烧死是我老婆的话　我会让他死两遍
If it was my wife I'd kill him twice.
我们进入达豪集中营大门的时候　纳粹军队直接投降
When we got through the gates of Dakau, the SS guards surrendered.
指挥官本想在我们到达之前自杀
The commandante tried to kill himself before we got there...
但他自杀技巧不怎么在行
but he botched it.
搞的最后过了一小时才死
Took him an hour to die.
我到外面的时候 看见地上都是尸体
When I went outside, I saw all the bodies on the ground.
多的数不胜数
Too many to count.
多的无法想象
Too many to imagine.
那些纳粹军队
So yeah
集体投降了　我们先让他们缴械　然后排成一排
The guards surrendered, we took their guns, we lined them up...
那不是战争
It wasn't warfare,
那是谋杀
it was murder.
我厌倦了杀人
Yeah I've had enough of killing.
我来这里不是为了报仇的
That's not why I'm here.
那是为了什么
So what is this all about?
雷德斯失踪以后
After Laeddis vanished,
我开始研究这精神病院
I started doing some checking on Ashecliffe.
很多人知道这个地方　但是没有人愿意讲
A lot of people knew about this place, but no one wants to talk...
好像害怕什么
You know? It's like they're scared of something.
这个地方经费来源是由特别基金赞助的
You know this place is funded by a special grant
来自于美国行动委员会
from the House of Unamerican Activities Committee.
在波士顿港的小岛上 要怎么和共产党作战?
HUAC. And how exactly are we fighting the Commies from an island in Boston Harbor?
通过进行心理实验
By conducting experiments on the mind.
我是这么认为的
At least that's my guess.
你觉得这里在进行心理实验?
And you think thats going on in here?
我说过　没人愿意谈论
Like I said, no one would talk, right?
但我后来找到一个以前在这里的病人
Until I found someone who used to be a patient here.
一个叫乔治诺伊斯的人
Guy's name is George Noyce.
很好的大学生 是个社会主义者
Nice college kid. Socialist.
他得到资金进行后心理研究 你猜他们在测试什么？
He gets offered some money to do a psych study. Guess what they were testing?
精神病的药－后来就出现很多脾气暴躁的人
- Tooth paste? - So he starts seeing dragons everywhere.
他差点把自己的教授打死 最后来到了隔离岛
Almost beats his professor to death Ends up here in Ashecliffe.
c栋病房
Ward C.
一年后把他重获自由　但他做了什么呢
They released him after 1 year, right? What does he do?
回到陆地三礼拜后　他就到酒吧里刺死了三个人
Two weeks on the mainland he walks into a bar and stabs three men to death.
诺伊斯的律师辩称是精神病
His lawyer pleads insanity, but Noyce...
但是他站在法庭上
Noyce, he stands up in the courtroom and
乞求法官判他死刑
he begs the judge, for the electric chair.
说什么不愿回到隔离岛来
Anywhere but a mental hospital.
法官没判处死刑　让他在戴德姆监狱服刑
Judge gives him life in Dedham prison.
你找到了他　对　我找到了他
- And you found him? - Yeah, I found him.
他根本不成人形
Well, he's a mess
但是他对我说的话却很明白
- But it's pretty clear from what he tells me, ... - What?
这里在进行特殊的人体实验
... they're experimenting on people here.
我不信
I don't know, boss.
不相信疯子的话　这就是好处
- How do you believe a crazy guy? - That's the beauty of it isn't it?
精神病人是最合适的试验品　 就算说出去也没有人相信
Crazy people are perfect subjects. They talk, but nobody listens.
我去过达豪集中营
I stood in Dakau.
我们见过人对人能做出什么残忍的事
We saw what human beings are capable of doing to each other, right?
为了阻止这种暴行　我们参加了战争
For Christ sake we fought a goddamn war
而如今这里却存在这种残忍的暴行？
to stop them, and now I find out it may be happening here?
在我们的国土上? 不行
On our soil? No.
那你来这里的真正目的是什么　泰德
So what are you really here to do, Teddy?
我来找证据
I'm gonna get the proof,
回去揭露这里的真相
I'm gonna go back, and blow the lid off this place.
这就是目的
That's it.
慢着
Wait a minute.
你一直在调查隔离岛
You started asking around about Ashecliffe.
就想找机会到这里来　而他们却恰恰需要一个 联邦警察　不可疑吗
Waiting for a chance to get out here then suddenly they need a US marshal?
是我运气好，有个病人逃走了 就成了我的借口
I got lucky. There was a patient escape, it was the perfect excuse.
不　老大　这不是运气
No, no, no boss. Luck doesn't work that way.
不是这样的　污水处理设施上都有电网
The world doesn't work that way. They got an electrified fence around a septic facility.
C栋病房还在内战时的堡垒里面
Ward C is inside a Civil War fort?
一个这的高层和纳粹党卫军有关联 资金又来自美国行动委员会
A chief of staff with ties to the OSS Funding from HUAC?
一切都说明这是政府刻意安排的
Jesus Christ! Everything about this place stinks of "government ops".
-或许是故意让你来这里　 -胡扯
- What If they wanted you here? - Bullshit.
-你可能一直被监控　 -胡说
- You were asking questions. - Bullshit.
胡说? 瑞秋的人呢？ 为什么没有她存在的一点点证据?
Bullshit? We came in for Rachel Solando? Where is one shred of evidence that she even existed?
他们不可能知道我被指派调查这件案子...
There's no way they could of known I'd be assigned to this case. No way...
你这是螳螂捕蝉黄雀在后
While you were looking into them, they were looking into you.
他们只需要编造个理由　把你引到这里
All they need to do is fake an escape to get you here.
现在把你引来了　把我们都引来了
And now they have you. Now they have us both, here, now.
警官　你在这里吗
Marshal, are you out here?
我是麦克弗森副典狱长
This is deputy warden McPherson.
联邦警察
Marshal!
怎么办　他们找到了我们
How about that? They found us huh.
这是个岛上　要找到我们还不简单
It's an island, boss. They're always gonna find us.
我知道你在里面
I know you are in there...
我们离开这个岛
We're getting off of this Goddamned island. You and me.
快
Come on!
- Come on! - Go!
换上干衣服 考利医生现在想见你们
Get dried off. Dr. Cawley wants to talk to you. Now!
快点 马上就变成飓风了
And hurry up, this thing is turning into a goddamn hurricane!
我把西装送去洗了
I dropped those suits off to be cleaned.
明天应该会好
It should be ready by tomorrow.
如果你们没有被冲走的话
That is if we don't all wash away first.
说到这一点　你们的烟已经湿掉不能抽了
Speaking of which, I'm afraid your smokes were pretty much done for.
所以...
So...
我们只能穿这种衣服
This is our only choice, huh?
这在监狱已经是不错的衣服了　不行吗
Got something really nice in prison already if that don't work for you...
这衣服可以
Now that you mention it, these are just fine.
因此我仍然坚持C栋病房的所有病人
That's why I must repeat my insistence that all ward C patients
都要上脚链严格看管
be placed in manual restraints.
如果淹水 会害死他们的 你是知道的
If the facility floods, they'll drown. You know that.
-这需要有很大的雨　 -我们在岛上
- That would take a lot of flooding. - We are on an island,
周围都是海洋又是飓风期间
in the middle of the ocean, during a hurricane.
淹大水是很有可能的
A lot of flooding seems like a distinct possibility.
应该要赌下去， 史蒂芬,假设供电失效的话
It's a gamble, Steven. Say the power fails, ...
我们还有备用发电机
There's a backup generator.
但若是停电　牢房门就会打开
And if that goes? The cell doors will open.
他们能去哪儿呢?
Where are they going to go?
不可能　跑到码头上　在飓风中游到其它陆地
They can't just hop a ferry, scoot over to the mainland and wreak havoc.
你说得对　他们只会跑到我们这里来
You're quite right. They're far more likely to wreak havoc right here on us.
如果他们带着脚铐 他们会因此丧命的
If they're manacled to the floor, they'll die.
这可是24条人命啊
That's 24 human beings.
你能承担的起吗？
You can live with that, can you?
说实话 如果我来做决定的话
Frankly, if it were up to me,
我会让A栋病房和B栋病房的42个人 直接集中由人工看管
I'd put all 42 in wards A and B in manual restraints as well.
打扰一下
Excuse me Excuse me
-警官　 -对不起先生　我只有一个小问题
- Marshal. - I'm sorry doctor, I just have one quick question.
我等一会就和你谈
Yes, I will be with you in a moment.
我们今天早上谈过有关 瑞秋索兰多留下的纸条
We spoke this morning about Rachel Solando's note.
"第四条定律"　我喜欢这句
The law of 4, I loved that.
你说你不明白第二句话什么意思是不是
You said you had no idea what that second line could refer to. Correct?
谁是67号
Who is 67?
我仍然不明白　我们都不明白
Yes, I'm afraid I still don't. None of us do.
一点都想不起来?
Uh huh. Nothing comes to mind.
一点都没有?
Nothing?
我刚才听你们说
Because I believe I just heard you say there are
C栋病房有24名病人
24 patients in ward C.
A栋病房和B栋病房有42个人
And 42 of patients, in wards A and B
这说明精神病院里有66名病人
Which means there is a total of what? 66 patients here in this facility.
没错
That is correct, yes.
那么瑞秋的意思是
Then it seems that Rachel Solando was suggesting
你们还有第67名病人　医生
that you have a 67th patient, doctor.
－但我们没有　太荒庸了
- But I'm afraid we don't. - This is ridiculous.
你到这里干什么　我到这里是为了工作
- What are you doing here? - We are doing our goddamn job.
麦克弗森没告诉你一个好消息吗
Didn't McPherson tell you the good news?
什么好消息
No, what's the good news, doctor?
瑞秋找到了
Rachel has been found.
她在这里
She's here.
非常安全
Safe and sound.
身上没有什么伤痕
There is not a mark on her.
这两人是谁
Who are these men?
为什么在我的房子里？
Why are they in my house?
他们是警察　瑞秋
Police officers, Rachel.
他们要问几个问题
They... have a few questions.
夫人
Ma'am.
有人看见一个匪谍
There's been a sighting of a known Communist
在这里搞破坏　散发传单
subversive in this area passing out literature
在这里?
Here?
在这小区里?
In this neighborhood?
是的
Yes, I'm afraid so.
告诉我们你昨天在哪里　做了什么
Now, if you can tell us what you did yesterday, where you were,
将会帮助我们缩小围捕范围
it would really help us narrow our search.
好
Yes...
我...
Well, I...umm
我为吉姆和孩子们做了早餐
I made breakfast for Jim and the children,
然后我...
and then I...
为吉姆包好便当  他就去上班了
I packed Jim's lunch and he left.
然后我送孩子们上学
Then I sent the children off to school.
然后...
And then...
我去湖里游泳
I decided to take a long swim in the lake.
我知道了
I see...
在这之后呢
And after that?
在这之后
After that...
我想起了你
I thought of you.
对不起夫人
I... I'm sorry, ma'am.
我不明白你的意思
I don't know what you're talking about.
你不知道我有多么孤独吗　吉姆?
Don't you know how lonely I've been, Jim?
你走了
You're gone...
你死了
You're dead.
我每天都掉眼泪
I cry every night.
我怎么活下去呢
How am I supposed to survive?
天啊
God.
瑞秋　会好起来的
Rachel... it will be all right.
我很对不起　不过
I'm so sorry, but...
一切都会好起来的
everything is gonna be all right? Okay?
我明明把你埋了
I buried you.
我埋了空棺材　你的尸体上都是血　我把你丢到到大海里
I buried an empty casket. Your body rained down lumps of flesh splashing
尸体全喂给鲨鱼了
into the sea eaten by sharks.
我的吉姆已经死了　你到底是谁
My Jim is dead, So who the fuck are you?
你到底是谁
Who the fuck are you?!
你是谁
Who are you?! Who are you?!
对不起
I'm sorry about that.
我本不想打断　我以为她会对你说出什么线索
I didn't want to interrupt, I thought she might tell you something, but...
我们在灯塔旁找到了她
we found her down by the lighthouse,
正在岩石上跳跃
skipping stones.
我们不知道她是怎么到了那里　我要请你们到地下室
We have no idea how she got out there. I'm going to ask you both to go down into basement.
那里有食物　水、床　在飓风到来的时候
There's food, water, and cots. It's the safest place to be
这是最安全的地方
when the hurricane hits.
你没事吧　你面色苍白
Are you all right? You look pale.
我没事　只是...
I'm fine, it's just uh...
老大你没事吧
Boss, are you okay?
只是太亮了点　不是吗
It's just so Goddamn bright? Isn't it?
感光　有时头疼　警官　你有偏头痛吗
Photo sensitivity, headaches sometimes? Marshal are you having a migraine?
我没事
I'll be alright.
吃了这药　过几个小时就好了
- What's wrong with him. - Take these, marshal. You'll sleep a couple of hours, wake up clear as a bell.
你这是偏头痛 就像有人在里面想锯开你的脑袋
He's having a migraine. Imagine someone sawed open your head and
用雷射使劲照你
filled it with razors then shook it as hard as they could.
把这药吃了吧 警官
Take the pills, marshal.
-我不想吃　 -这能镇痛　吃药吧
- No... I don't want the pills. - It'll stop the pain. Take the pills.
你需要躺下
He's going to need to lie down.
上帝!
Oh God!
小心点 好了
Careful. All right.
不会有事的
Gonna be okay. Relax.
那是谁　他吗
- Who is that? - Him?
他是典狱长
That's the warden.
别管他了
Don't you worry about him, alright?
看来是个退休军官的混蛋
Looks like an ex-military prick.
这一点我不能发表看法
You know what? I ain't gonna argue with you on that one.
你应该要救我的
You should have saved me.
你应该要救了我们所有人
You should have saved all of us.
嘿　兄弟
Hey buddy.
嘿.
Hey.
雷德斯
Laeddis.
是的
Yes.
嘿　兄弟
Hi, buddy.
不再生气了吧
No hard feelings, right?
别再生气了
No hard feelings.
留给你以后喝
Little something for later.
我知道你多么需要
Because I know how much you need it.
时间片刻不停. 我的朋友
Clock's ticking, my friend.
我们时间不多了
We're running out of time.
帮我一下
Give me a hand here.
我会惹上麻烦的
I could get into trouble.
我死了吗
I'm dead?
对不起
I'm so sorry.
你为什么不救我
Why didn't you save me?
我也想救你　但是我赶到的时候
I tried, I wanted to, but by the time I got there,
已经太晚了
it was too late.
看
See?
多美啊
Aren't they beautiful?
你为什么全身都湿了
Why are you all wet, baby?
雷德斯没有死
Laeddis isn't dead.
他没有走
He isn't gone.
他还在这里
He's still here.
我知道
I know.
我需要找到他　泰德
We need to find him, Teddy.
你找到他　把他杀死
You need to find him and you kill him dead.
没关系
Shhh. It's okay.
A栋病房我知道了
Shh. Again!
发电机出现故障
The generator is flooded.
你没事吧 老大
Are you okay boss?
该死的偏头痛
This goddamn migraine!
备用发电机坏了　这里整个一团混乱
Back up generators failed. The whole place has gone crazy.
你想干什么
What do you want to do?
天啊
Christ!
不不 放下来
No, no, no! Put it down.
快　快
Now! Now!
整个供电系统都瘫痪了?
You think the whole electrical system is fried?
很可能
I'd say that it's a good possibility.
所有的电子保全系统
All electronic security...
围墙电网　大门
fences, gates, the doors
快
Come on.
这是散步的好时候
Nice day for a stroll don't you think?
比如到C栋病房散个步
To ward C for example.
或许你会碰到安德鲁雷德斯
Maybe we'll run into Andrew Leaddis.
我给你说过的那个人　乔治诺伊斯
The guy I told you about, George Noyce?
他说真正的狠脚色都在这里
He told me this is where they keep the worse ones.
连其它病房的人都怕他们
The guys even the other inmates are scared of.
诺伊斯说过实验室的事吗
Noyce give you anything on the layout?
没有
Not really.
他只记得人们从早到晚都在惨叫　没有窗户
All that he remembers was people scream day and night. There were no windows.
到处都是栅栏
There were bars everywhere.
天啊
Jesus Christ!
第一次到C栋病房吧
First time on ward C, right?
是的
- Yes, yes... - Yes.
我们听说...　相信我　你们听说的都是胡扯的
- Yeah, heard stories, but... - Trust me, sons. You haven't heard shit.
多数病人都关起来了
We got most of the bugsies locked down now,
但还有一些人在外面
But some of them are still loose.
如果见到了　不要试图凭自己制服他
If you see one don't try to restrain him yourselves.
这些混蛋会杀了你们
These fuckers will kill you.
明白吗
Clear?
好了　进去吧
Alright. Get your asses moving then. Go on.
他在这里
He's here.
雷德斯
Laeddis.
我能感觉到他
I can feel him.
碰到了　换当鬼抓我了
Tag! You're it.
泰德
Ted!
听我说
Listen to me!
听着　我不想离开好么
Listen! I do not want to leave, all right?
为什么有人不想呢　我听说过这里的很多事情
Why would anyone want to? We hear things here.
关于外面的世界　关于珊瑚礁
About the outside world. About atolls.
关于氢弹测试
About the h-bomb tests.
你知道氢弹是怎么作的
You know how a hydrogen bomb works?
用　氢气　真好笑
- With... Hydrogen? - That's funny.
别的炸弹是会爆炸
- Boss! - Other bombs explode, right?
但是氢弹不会 它是内部溶掉的
But not the hydrogen bomb It implodes.
瞬间会产生好几百万度的高温
Creating an explosion to the thousandth millionth degree.
-了解了吗? -是的　是
- Do you get it? - Yeah. Yeah.
是么　我明白了
- Do you? - I get it!
滚吧
Let em go!
不
No!
你干嘛呢
What are you doing?
上帝　泰德　天
Jesus Christ, Teddy. Jesus!
你抓到了比尔了
You got Billings?
你们到底在干嘛　是抓住他们　不是杀了他们
What's the fuck's the matter with you guys? You catch them, not kill them!
他扑过来攻击我
He jumped us.
你来帮我一把　我们把他弄到医务室去
You, give me a hand with him. We've got to get him to the infirmary.
可恶!
Goddamnit!
-不　不是你　 -去四处逛逛吧
No, no! Not you, not you. Take a walk.
快点
Come on!
去你的屋顶上吧
Paula's gonna have my Goddamn balls for this..
雷德斯
Laeddis....
求求你
Please...
上帝
Oh my God!
在我杀掉更多人之前阻止我
Stop me. Before I kill more.
雷德斯 ...
Laeddis ...
去吧
Go!
拜托　拜托
Please, please!
雷德斯
Laeddis ...
你说过我自由了
You told me I'd be free of this place.
你保证过的
You promised.
你骗人!
You lied.
雷德斯
Laeddis?
真他妈的有趣
That's pretty damned funny.
你的声音
Your voice...
你听不出来么
Don't you recognize it?
我们说了那么多话
After all the talks we had?
你对我说了那么多谎
After all the lies you've told me?
给我看看你的脸
Let me see your face.
他们说我是他们的了
They say I'm theirs now.
他们说我永远也走不了
They say I'll never leave here.
你的对手就要出去了
Your match is about to go out.
给我看看你该死的脸
Let me see your goddamn face now!
为什么
Why?
所以你还继续说谎吗?
So you can lie to me more?
这跟真相无关　不 有关系
- This isn't about the truth! - Yes it is.
跟曝光有关　这跟你有关
- It's about exposing the truth. - This is about you!
还有　雷德斯
And Laeddis.
这一切都有关的
That's all it's ever been about.
我是偶然
I was incidental.
进来的
A way in.
乔治?
George?
乔治诺伊斯
George Noyce?
不　不可能　你不可能在这的
No, it's not possible, You can't be here.
你喜欢吗?
Do you like it?
谁把你弄成这样的　乔治
Who did this to you, George?
你
You did!
你什意思
What the hell do you mean?
你说的是什么意思
What are you talking all of your fucking talk
我回来这都是因为你
And I'm back here because of you!
乔治　我把你弄出去
George, I how did they get you out of Dedham. Huh?
我会想办法弥补的
However this happened, Im gonna find a way to fix this. You understand me?
我再也出不去了
I'll never get out now.
我出去过一次　但没有第二次了
I got out once, But not twice, never twice.
告诉我他们怎么把你弄这来的　他们知道
- Tell me how they got you here? - They knew!
你不明白吗
Don't you get it?
你做的一切　你的全部计划
Everything you were up to. Your whole plan.
这是个游戏　这一切
This is a game. All of this...
都是为你准备的
is for you.
你不是在调查
You're not investigating anything.
你就是迷宫里的一只小老鼠
You're a fucking rat in a maze.
乔治
George...
你错了
Gearge you're wrong.
是么
Really?
你不都一直就一个人吗
Been alone much since you got here?
我有个搭档
I'm been with my partner.
你没和他一起工作过　对么
You have never worked with him before, have you?
他是个
He's a...
从西雅图来的警察
US Marshal from Seattle.
但你从没和他一起工作过对吧?
You have never worked with him before, have you?
乔治 听着
George, look...
我了解人们我相信他
I know people. I trust this man.
那么　他们已经赢了
Then, they've already won.
该死
Fuck!
他们要
They're going to...
带我去灯塔
take me to the lighthouse.
他们要扒开我的大脑
They're going to cut into my brain.
都是因为你我才在这的
And I'm only here because of you!
乔治!我会把你弄出去的　你不用去灯塔
George, I'm going to get you out of here. You're not going to the lighthouse.
你不可
You're not.
你不可能同时杀掉雷德斯并揭露真相
You can't dig out the truth and kill Laeddis at the same time.
你得做个选择　明白吗?
You've got to make a choice. You understand that, don't you?
我不是来杀人的
I'm not here to kill anyone.
-骗子　 -我没杀他　我发誓...
- Liar! - I not gonna kill him! I swear to you ...
她死了
She's dead.
让她走吧
Let her go...
Let her go.
泰德　告诉他
Tell him Teddy...
告诉他 这是怎么一回事
Tell him why.
你必须这么做,没有别的办法了
You've got to do it. There's no other way.
放她走　你给我拿这些花时...
- Let her go. - Tell him about the day you brought me my locket...
你就该做了
You've gotta do it!
我权告诉你　你却伤了我的心　 现在你问我原因?
How I told you my heart was breaking. And you asked me why?
自己想想吧
She's fucking with your head.
然后我告诉你它来自于幸福
And I told you it was from happiness.
她要杀你
She'll kill you. She's going to kill you.
你想揭开真相?那么你得让她走
You want to uncover the truth? You've gotta let her go ...
-我不能　 -你必须让她走
- I can't. - You have to let her go!
我不能　我不能
I can't! I can't.
那么你永远没法离开这座岛
Then you'll never leave this island.
雷德斯
Dolores?
他不在这个病房了
He's not in this ward.
他被移送
He was transferred...
出去了
Out of here.
如果他不在A栋病房
If he's not in ward A,
那只可能在一个地方了.
there's only one place he can be
-灯塔
The lighthouse.
嘿
Hey!
上帝保佑你
God help you.
老大　有麻烦了　考利和麦克弗森到了c栋里
Boss, we got problems. McPherson and Cawley are in the building.
考利听说有个病人被看护殴打
They heard an orderly went batshit on a patient,
那人逃到屋顶上　他上去找他了
They're looking all over the place for him. They're on the way to the roof.
我们快离开这
Let's get the hell out of here.
走这边
This way.
-快走　 -镇定点,我们现在是看护
Just keep going. We belong here
-你刚怎么了 -什么意思?
- What happened to you? - What do you mean?
你到哪去了?
Where were you?
我们把他这到医务室以后
After we got that guy to the infirmary,
我溜到档案室 翻了一下病人记录
I took a little detour to patient records.
你找到雷德斯了吗?
Did you ever find Laeddis?
没有
No.
-没,没找到　 -我找到了更好的东西
- No. I never found him. - Well I've got the next best thing.
-他的入院登记表
His intake form.
在他的档案夹,没有会议记录,没有事件报告
It was the only thing in his file. No session notes. No incident reports.
没有任何照片　很奇怪
No photographs... just this. It was weird.
拿去 你看看
Here, take a look.
待会儿我再看
I'll look at it later.
怎么了 老大
What's the matter, boss?
我只是想等会再看
I'll take a look at it later, that's all.
我们应该往那边走
Ashecliffe's that way.
我不去回去监狱那边
I'm not going to Ashecliffe.
我要去灯塔
I'm going to the lighthouse.
我要搞清楚这岛上到底发生了什么
I'm going to find out what the fuck is happening on this island.
就这里了
Here it is.
该死的
Damn!
太远了　我们得回头
We're too far South. We're gonna have to double back.
没有办法穿过这些岩石
There's no way we could cross those rocks.
那些树后面 应该会有路的
There could be a way behind those trees.
也许是一条穿过岩石到达灯塔的小路
Maybe a path that goes around the rocks that leads over to the lighthouse.
等等,到底来这干嘛 我们拿到了他的入院登记表
What are we doing here? We've got the intake form.
那证明这里有他们说不存在的67号病人
It proves there's a 67th patient... which they've said repeatedly doesn't exist.
我就是要去那个灯塔　你懂吗?
I'm getting to that lighthouse. Do you understand?
我怎么说你才能停下来呢
What the hell can I say to you to stop you?
为何你要阻止我?为什么?
Why would you want to Chuck? Why?
我阻止你是因为天一黑什么看不到.. 这样爬下去跟自杀没什么两样
Because climbing down there when it's dark is a thin step short to suicide. That's why.
好吧
Okay.
也许你坐这看着会发生什么事
Maybe you better sit this one out then.
你让我淌这趟浑水　老大　现在我身陷其中,卡在岩壁里了
You brought me into this, boss. And now I am trapped here on this rock.
在这岛上
On this island.
这里没人认识我们　你现在像...
Without no one to rely on but eachother. And now you're acting like.........
像什么
Like what? Like what?
我像在演戏吗
How am I acting?
刚在C栋里到底发生了什么　泰德
What the hell happened back there in those cells, Ted?
-你觉得波特兰的天气怎样　查克　 -我来自西雅图
- What do you think the weather is like in Portland, Chuck? - I'm from Seattle.
西雅图
Seattle?
我要过去 自己过去!
I'll going on...alone.
我跟你一起　老大
I'm going with you, boss.
我说了我自己去
I said alone.
好吧
Fine.
该死!
Damn it!
该死
我们方位偏差太多 而且我过不去　因为涨潮了
I knew it wouldn't take long. But I couldn't get to it. The tide was up.
查克
Chuck!
过来点!
Come on!
查克
Chuck!
你在哪　查克
Where are you, Chuck?
查克
Chuck!
你是谁
Who are you?
我是泰德丹尼尔
I'm Teddy Daniels.
我是警察
I'm a cop.
你是联邦警察
You're the marshal.
是的
That's right.
你介意
Would you mind...
把手从后面拿出来吗?
taking your hand from behind your back, please?
为什么?
Why?
Why?!
为了确认你手里的东西不会伤害我
I want to make sure what you're holding won't hurt me.
我要拿着...
I'm gonna keep this...
如果你不介意的话
If you don't mind.
我不介意
Fine by me.
你是瑞秋索兰多
You're Rachel Solando.
真正的那个
The real one.
你杀了你的孩子们么
Did you kill your children?
我没有孩子
I never had children.
我没有结过婚
I was never married.
在成为隔离岛的病人前　我在这工作
And before I was a patient in Ashecliff, I worked here.
你是护士
You were a nurse?
我是精神科医生　警官
I was a doctor, marshal.
你觉得我疯了么
You think I'm crazy?
不　我　如果我说我没疯
- No, I ... - And if I say I'm not crazy ...
但那也是没有用　对吧
well that hardly helps, does it?
那是白痴的想法
That's the Kafkaesque genius of it.
人们总是告诉你 你疯了
People tell the world you're crazy
就是跟你对立抗争
and all your protests to the contrary,
要你相信他们说的一切
just confirms what they're saying.
我没有听懂你说的　很抱歉
I'm not following you. I'm sorry.
一旦你承认疯了
Once you are declared insane,
那你做的一切就是疯了
then anything you do is called a part of that insanity.
不管是理智的抵抗还是否认
Your reasonable protests or denial.
恐惧还是妄想 你都会被认为你是疯了
Valid fears, paranoia.
生存的本能
Survival instincts.
就像自我防御
Defense mechanisms.
警官,你比看起来精明多了　 但这也许不是件好事
You're smarter than you look marshal. That's probably not a good thing.
告诉我
Tell me something...
好的
Yeah...
你发生了什么
What happened to you?
刚开始我问他们为何要购买运送大量的钠
I started asking about these large shipments of sodium-anatol
含有钠原料的致幻剂　 是治疗精神病的药物
- and opium-based hallucinogens. - Psychotropic drugs.
我还问了些有关于手术的事情
I asked about the surgeries, too.
有听过前额叶切除手术吗?
Ever heard of trans-orbital lobotomy?
他们先用电击疗法控制病人
They zap the patient with electroshocks,
然后用冰钻穿过眼睛
then go through the eye with an ice pick
接着挑掉一些神经组织
and pull out some nerve fibers.
让病人更加听话
Makes the patients much more obedient.
更好驯服
Tractable.
太野蛮了
It's barbaric.
太荒谬了
Unconscionable.
警官, 你知道身体有多痛吗?
Do you know how pain enters the body marshal? Do you?
那取决于你伤了哪里
Depends on where you're hurt.
不　跟肉体没关系
No, it has nothing to do with the flesh.
大脑控制疼痛
The brain controls pain.
大脑控制着恐惧　情绪　睡眠　生气　饥饿一切
The brain controls fear, empathy, sleep, hunger, anger... everything.
如果你能控制它呢
What If you could control it?
大脑
The brain?
重新创造一个人
Re-create a man,
那么他将感觉不到疼痛
so he doesn't feel pain,
或者爱　或是同情
or love, or sympathy.
一个什么都不会被拷问出来的人　 因为他没有任何记忆去坦白
A man who can't be interrogated because he has no memories to confess.
他们不可能拿走所有人的记忆
You can never take away all a man's memories.
永远不可能
Never.
你知道么　北韩在洗脑实验中
Marshal, the North Koreans used American POWs
使用美国战俘试验
during their brainwashing experiments.
他们把士兵变成叛徒　在这里他们就是这么做的
They turned soldiers into traitors. That's what they are doing here.
神志清楚的人是不会在世上创造鬼怪说
They're creating ghosts to go out in the world. And do things sane men never do.
那种能力与知识
To have that kind of ability, that kind of knowledge.
那需要长时间研究才办得的
That would take years.
长年的研究 对成百上千病人的实验
Years of research, hundreds of patients to experiment on.
50年来　人们回头看时
50 years from now, people will look back
他们会说 一切就是从这开始的
and say, "Here. This place is where it all began."
纳粹使用犹太人
The Nazis used the Jews.
苏联人用古格拉集中营中的犯人 而我们...
The Soviets used prisoners  in their own gulags, and we...
我们拿病患做实验
We tested patients,
隔离岛上的病患
on Shutter Island.
不,他们不会 不
No, they won't ... No
你其实知道
You do understand
他们不会让你离开　对吧?
That they can't let you leave?
我是联邦警察
I am a federal marshal ...
他们不能阻止我
They can't stop me.
我曾是个受人敬重的精神科医生
I was an esteemed psychiatrist,
来自一个备受敬仰的医生家族
from a respected family.
那一点也没有用
It didn't matter.
我问你
Let me ask you ...
你曾有过精神创伤吗？
any past traumas in your life?
有啊　跟这一切有什么关系?
Yes. Why? Why would that matter?
他们要让你有一个过去的事件
Because they can point to some event in your past and say
可以推说那是你丧失神智的一部份原因
it is the reason you lost your sanity
那么当他们把你困在这里时
So that when they commit you here
你的朋友　同事会说... 他突然就这样爆发了
your friends and colleagues will say, "Of course he cracked."
谁都会这样说
"And who wouldn't have, after what he'd been through."
你说的可能发生在任何一个人身上
They can say that about anyone
-任何人都有可能 -重点是他们目前是锁定你
- anyone at all. - The point is they're going to say it about you.
你的头还好吗？
How's your head?
-我的头？　 -来这后一直作怪梦吗？
- My head? - Any funny dreams lately?
糟糕的睡眠　头痛
Trouble sleeping? Headaches?
我可能得了偏头痛
I am prone to migraines. Yes.
天啊
Jesus!
你没吃他们的药吧?
You haven't taken any pills, have you?
-连阿司匹灵也没吃吧? -我吃了一片阿司匹灵
- I mean even aspirin? - They hit the aspirin?
天杀的..
Jesus!
你有在食堂 喝咖啡或吃了什么吗
And you ate the food in the cafeteria and drank coffee they gave you.
别告诉我你还抽了他们给你的烟
You tell me at least that you've been smoking your own cigarettes.
不
No... no.
我都有..
No. I haven't.
神精麻醉剂需要36到48小时
It takes 36 to 48 hours for neuroleptic narcotics
充分接触血液　然后发挥作用
to reach workable levels in the blood stream.
先是脉搏
Palsy comes first
手指　然后所有的身体部位
First the fingertips and then eventually the whole hand.
警官　你最近做恶梦么
Seen any walking nightmares  lately, marshal? Huh?
告诉我灯塔里发生了什么
Tell me what goes on in that lighthouse?
告诉我
Tell me.
大脑手术
Brain surgery.
就像　打开颅骨看里面怎样
"Let's open the skull and see what happens if we pull on this" kind.
跟纳粹的手法如出一辙
"We learned it from the Nazi's" kind.
接着他们创造出来鬼魂
It's where they create the ghosts.
谁知道这事
Who knows about this?
我是说在岛上　谁
On the island I mean. Who?
人人都知道
Everyone.
拜托　护士吗?看护??
Oh come on. The nurses? The orderlies?
不可能...岛上每个人都心知肚明
- They couldn't possibly know... - Everyone.
你不能再待在这了
You can't stay here.
他们以为我死了　淹死的　 如果他们来这找你就会发现我
They think I'm dead, that I drowned. I'm afraid if they come looking for you, they might find me.
很抱歉　但你得走了
I'm sorry, but you have to go.
我会回来找你的
I'm gonna come back for you.
我不会在这了　我天天换地方　每晚都是个新地方
I won't be here. I move during the day. new places every night.
但我可以带你离开这个岛
But I could come get you off of this island.
我刚才说的 你都没听进去吗?
Haven't you heard a word I've said?
只有渡轮可以离开这座岛　他们还控制着渡轮
The only way off the island is the ferry and they control it.
你永远也无法离开这里
You'll never leave here.
我有个朋友
I had a friend.
他昨天和我在一起　但我们走散了
I was with him yesterday, but we got separated.
你有看到他吗?
Have you seen him?
联邦警察
Marshal...
你没有任何朋友
You have no friends.
你在这啊
There you are.
我们正好奇 你到底何时会出现呢
We've been wondering when you'd show up.
坐吧
Have a seat.
来吧
Come on.
在隔离岛散步的怎样?
Taking a leisurely stroll? Were we?
我
I was just...
只是在四处转转
just looking around.
享受上帝刚给的礼物吗?
Did you enjoy God's latest gift?
什么　上帝的礼物
- What? - God's gift.
暴力
The violence.
当我从家里楼上下来看见横躺在客厅的大树时
When I came downstairs in my home and I saw that tree in my living room,
就像是上帝把手伸到我面前一样
it reached down for me like a divine hand.
上帝喜欢暴力
God loves violence.
-我没注意　 -你当然注意到了
- I hadn't noticed. - Sure you have.
不然会有这么多暴力呢
Why else would there be so much of it?
就在我们中间
It's in us.
这就是人性啊
It's what we are.
我们发动战争　四处放火抢劫
We wage war, we burn sacrifices, we pillage and plunder
然后处理兄弟的遣体
and tear at the flesh of our brothers
为什么　因为上帝以他的名义让我们发起暴力
and why? Because God gave us violence to wage in his honor.
我以为上帝给我们是道德的指令
I thought God gave us moral order.
没有像这飓风一样纯粹的道德指令
There is no moral order as pure as this storm.
根本没有道德的指令
There's no moral order at all.
仅有的是　我的暴力能否战胜你的
There's just this: can my violence conquer yours?
-我不暴力　 -不,你是暴力份子
- I'm not violent. - Yes you are.
你和他们一样
You're as violent as they come.
我会知道是因为 我也和他们一样
I know this because I'm as violent as they come.
来自我们构造的幻想世界
With the constraints of society, we are lifted and
如果我跟你的食物站在一起 你会用石头敲碎我的脑壳 然后抢走我的食物
If I was all that stood between you and a meal, you would crack my skull with a rock and eat my meaty parts.
可怜的你
Wouldn't you?
考利觉得你没有威胁　你可以被控制　 但我知道你不一样
Cawley thinks you're harmless, that you can be controlled, but I know different.
-你并不了解我　 -我其实一清二楚
- You don't know me. - Oh but I do. Oh I know you.
我们彼此了解了几个世纪了
We've known each other for centuries.
如果现在我把牙齿插入你的眼睛
If I was to sink my teeth into your eye right now,
你能在我把你弄瞎前阻止我吗?
would you be able to stop me before I blinded you?
你敢的话就试试看
Give it a try.
就是这种精神
That's the spirit.
你去哪了
Where have you been?
瞎逛四处看看你的岛
Wandering, just looking at your island.
你该走了　瑞秋找到了
Oh I forgot. You're leaving. Now that Rachel has been found.
当然
Sure. Yeah.
大会议
Big meeting?
哦　是的
Oh, yes ...
显然昨天C栋病房混进一个身份不明的人
Apparently there was an unidentified man in ward C yesterday
他空手制服了一个危险的病人
He subdued a highly dangerous patient. Quite handily.
然后呢
Is that so?
似乎他和一个偏执狂　 精神病患者聊了很久　乔治诺伊斯
It seems he had a long conversation with a paranoid schizophrenic, George Noyce.
这个诺伊斯你说他的名字是
This Noyce, you said his name was,
他是偏执狂　是么　哦　是的 他很不安
- he's delusional? - Oh extremely. He can be quite upsetting.
事实上　两周前　一个病人
In fact, two weeks ago, a patient got so wound up
在伊斯的楼层晃了太久 被他吃掉了
by one of Noyce's stories that he beat him up.
抽烟吗?
Cigarette?
不　谢谢　我戒了
Oh. No, thanks. I quit.
那么　你要搭渡轮么
So, you're taking the ferry?
当然
Oh yes. Absolutely. I uh...
我想我们已经得到了需要的一切
I think we've gotten all we came here for so.
你说"我们"　联邦警察?
"We" marshal?
既然你提到,
Speaking of which. Have you
-你看见他了吗,医生?　 -谁?
- seen him, Doctor? - Who?
我的搭档　查克
My partner, Chuck.
你哪来的搭档　警官　你自己来的
You don't have a partner, Marshal. You came here alone.
你知道吗? 我建造了一些有价值的东西
You know, I've built something valuable here.
但是有价值的东西 在他们那个时代总是被误解
And valuable things have a way of being misunderstood in their own time.
人人都想快点好起来　他们总是那样
Everyone wants a quick fix, they always have.
我试着做一些人们甚至是你也不理解的
I'm trying to do something that people, yourself included, don't understand.
没经过奋战 我是不会放弃的
And I'm not going to give up without a fight.
我知道
I can see that...
那你刚提到你的搭档?
So tell me again about your partner.
什么搭档?
What partner?
警官
Marshal...
你要到哪去呢?
Going somewhere?
我要往那去码头搭渡轮
No. Just heading out to the ferry. So...
码头在另外一头才对
I'm afraid it's the other way.
你稍等下
If you wait a moment,
我找人带你去码头
I'll find someone who can take you to the dock.
这是什么　医生
What is this, doctor?
只是镇静剂
It's just a sedative.
-以防万一的　 -以防万一?
- It's for precaution. - Precaution?
你要干嘛　杀了我吗?
What are you going to do? Kill me? Marshal.
你值得我这么做吗?
You think you deserve it?
什么?　激怒你?
For what? For provoking you?
请原谅我,但现在不是任何事都可以激怒你?
and, forgive me, what doesn't provoke you?
谈论
Remarks...
-字词　 -纳粹
- Words... - Nazis!
也是
Well that, too.
当然　也包括 记忆　梦
And of course, memories, dreams...
你知道么外伤一词来自希腊文
Did you know that the word "trauma" comes from the Greek for "wound"?
德语中的梦叫做　梦境
And what is the German word for "dream" "Traumen".
梦境　梦
Traumen.
伤口可以造出怪兽
Wounds can create monsters.
然而你　你受伤了,警官
And you ... you are wounded, marshal.
我知道你同意　当你看见怪兽时
Wouldn't you agree, when you see a monster
你必须停下来
you must stop it?
-我同意　 -是的
- I agree. - Yes...
你在干麻,宝贝?
What are you doing, baby?
你该去搭渡轮了
You've got to get to the ferry.
不　不
No. No. No.
如果人们认为查克死了， 那他将成为他们的试验品
If the world thinks that Chuck is dead, then he is perfect for their experiments.
他们只会带他到一个地方
There's only one place they'd take him.
你如果去了灯塔　你也会死
You go there and you'll die.
他是我搭档, 我必须去救他
He's my partner. If they are hurting him, if they are holding him against his will, I've got to bring him out.
我不能再失去任何人了
I can't lose anyone else.
别去那　别去　泰德
Don't go, Teddy. Please don't do this. Don't go.
抱歉　宝贝
I'm sorry, honey.
我喜欢这条领带　 因为是你买给我的
I love this thing because you gave it to me
但事实是
But the truth is ...
这领带实在丑到爆
it's one fucking ugly tie.
不
No!
别动　待着别动
Don't move! Stay where you are!
你要杀了我吗？
Are you going to kill me?
不 我不会杀你
No. I'm not gonna kill you.
你为何湿透了,宝贝？
Why are you all wet, baby?
-你说什么？ -你知道我在说什么
- What did you say? - You know exactly what I said.
顺带一提　那枪没子弹
The rifle's empty by the way.
请坐
Have a seat.
把衣服换下来吧　你会感冒的
For god's sake dry off you're going to catch a cold.
好吧
Alright.
你把警卫打得很严重吗？
How badly did you hurt the guard?
我不明白你的意思
I don't know what you're talking about.
是的　他在这
Yes. He's here.
送他送上来前 希恩医生有看过他了吗?
Have Dr.Sheehan take a good look at your man before you send him up.
那么　希恩医生
So, Dr. Shehan...
今早搭了渡轮来这?
He came on the ferry this morning, huh?
没有
Not exactly.
你炸了我的汽车　我真的很爱那辆车
You blew up my car. I really loved that car.
很抱歉
Sorry to hear about that.
你颤抖的情况更加严重了
Tremors are getting pretty bad.
幻觉的状况呢
How are the hallucinations?
走吧　泰德
Get out of here, Teddy.
你会死在这里的
This place is gonna be the end of you.
-没那么糟　 -明明都又变糟了
- Not bad. - They'll get worse.
我知道
I know.
索兰多医生
Dr. Solando...
告诉我关于神经幻觉的事情
she told me about neuroleptics.
她知道? 什么时候的事?
Did she now? And when was this?
我找到了她　在峭壁的山洞里　但你抓不到她
I found the doctor, in a cave out by the cliffs. But you'll never get to her.
我不怀疑
I don't doubt it.
你想的那些不是真的
Considering she's not real.
但是你的幻觉 比我估算的还严重
But your hallucinations are more severe than I thought.
你没有吃精神松弛剂
You are not on neuroleptics.
事实上你没有服用精神松弛剂
You are not on anything as a matter of fact.
那这是什么 这是什么
Then what the fuck is this? Huh, what the fuck is this?
后遗症
Withdrawal.
Withdrawal?
什么后遗症　来这个岛上以后我连酒都没喝过
From what? I haven't even had a Goddamned drink since I've been on this island.
精神病药物
Chlorpromazine.
我不是药理学的专家　但是看了你的病例
I'm not a fan of pharmacology but I have to say in your case ...
精神..　 你说那是什么　精神病药物
- Clorpro... what? - Chlorpromazine.
跟过去的两年 我们开给你的药一样
The same thing we've been  giving you for the past 24 months.
所以过去的两年
So for the past two years
你们安排人偷偷再在波士顿给我下药？
you've had somebody slipping me drugs in Boston. Is that it?
不是波士顿 是这里
Not Boston. Here.
你已经在这两年了　 你是这里的病患
You've been here for two years. A patient of this institution.
医生　看过这里的一切以后
After everything I seen here, doctor,
你认为你能说服我　 我疯了吗?
you really think you're gonna convince me I'm crazy, huh?
你知道我们对付的是怎样的人吗？ 我可是美国联邦警察
Do you know the kind of people I deal with everyday? I'm a U.S. marshal. For Gods sake.
你曾是美国联邦警察 这有一份你的入院申请表的副本
You were a U.S. marshal. Here's a copy of the intake form.
你闯入C栋病房 为了证明67号病人
You broke into ward C for proof of the 67th patient
如果你回到大陆　你会炸了这里
If you'd gotten it to the mainland, you could have blown the lid off this place.
等等　但是
- Wait... wait. - But somehow
你还没时间亲眼看看这　看看吧
you couldn't find time to look at it. Well read it now.
拿去看
Go ahead.
病人极度聪明　极度的错觉症
The patient is highly intelligent, highly delusional.
幻觉常是军队老兵装扮
Decorated army veteran.
因参与达卡夫解放战役而被监禁
Present for the liberation of Dakau.
前美国联邦警察
Former U.S. marshal.
有暴力倾向
Known proclivity for violence.
对罪责没有任何悔恨
Shows no remorse for his crime  because he denies
因为他否认他犯过罪
that the crime ever took place. Highly developed and fantastical
建构完整复杂的故事剧情 阻碍他 面对自己行为的真相
narratives which preclude facing the truth of his actions.
我不想看这些狗屁
I've had enough of this bullshit.
我的搭档在哪
Where's my partner, huh?
查克在哪　他在哪
Where's Chuck? Where is he?
我们试试别的方法吧
Let's try this another way.
你妻子的小名字叫　 恰娜　对吗？
Your wife's maiden name was "Chanal". Am I correct?
别提到她　很抱歉我必须这么做
- Don't you even talk about her! - I'm afraid I have to.
注意这四个名字 有相同的地方吗？
Notice anything these four names have in common?
规则4
Your rule of 4.
安德鲁你看到了什么　如果你
- Andrew, what do you see? - If you have done anything
-对我搭档做了什么 医生 这是侵害人权的事 -注意点　安德鲁你看到了什么
- to my partner, doctor. That is a violation ... - Focus, Andrew. What do you see?
这些名字　有同样的字母
The names ... have the same letters.
爱德华　丹尼尔和
Edward Daniels has exactly the same 13 letters
安德鲁雷德斯　有同样的13个字母　瑞秋和索兰多也是
as Andrew Laeddis. The same as Rachel Solando
还有多洛雷斯陈　所有的名字
and Dolores Chanal.
-都是字母顺序的变异 -你唬不了我的
- The names are anagrams for each other.
对我无效
Your tactics, they're not going to work on me.
你来这里找出真相　这就是真相
You came here for the truth. Here it is.
你叫安德鲁雷德斯
Your name is Andrew Laeddis.
隔离岛的67号病人就是你　安德鲁
The 67th patient at Ashecliffe is you, Andrew.
胡扯
Bullshit.
两年前你被法院判刑到这里
You were committed here by court order 24 months ago.
你犯的罪很可怕 你无法原谅自己
Your crime is terrible. One you can't forgive yourself for.
于是你创造了另一个自己
So you invented another self.
给我回到现实世界
Let's get down to the facts.
你创造了一个没有被杀死的故事
You've created a story in which you're not a murderer, you are hero.
你是美国联邦警察
Still a U.S marshal.
在这隔离岛　侦办一个案子
Only here at Ashecliffe because of a case
你想揭露了其中阴谋
and you've uncovered a conspiracy
所以我们告诉你的真相 你是谁 你做了什么
so that anything we tell you about who you are, what you've done
不管说什么你都认为是个谎言　安德鲁
you can dismiss as lies, Andrew.
我叫爱德华丹尼尔
My name is Edward Daniels.
我两年来一直听你说这奇特的故事 所以我知道一切细节
I've been hearing this fantasy for two years now. I know every detail.
67号病人 飓风 瑞秋索兰多
Patient 67. The storm. Rachel Solando.
你走失的搭档　每晚都做的梦
Your missing partner. The dreams you have every night.
你是去过达卡夫　但不可能杀了所有的纳粹警卫
You were at Dakau, But you may not have killed any guards.
我希望我能让你活在你幻想的虚构世界里
I wish I could let you just live in your fantasy world.
我真的想那样
I really do.
但是你太暴力　受过训练　太危险 你是这里最危险的病人
But you're violent, trained, dangerous. You're the most dangerous patient we have.
你伤害了所有的警卫　其它病人
You've injured orderlies. Guards. Other patients.
两周前　你袭击了乔治诺伊斯
Two weeks ago you attacked George Noyce.
我没做那些
No, no! I am fucking on to you doctor!
你...我当然没有
- You had Noyce beaten. - Of course I didn't.
你给我个我会攻击他的理由
Give me one reason why I would even touch him.
因为他叫你雷德斯
Because he called you Laeddis
你做了一切事情 让你不要变成他
and you do anything not to be him.
我这有你昨天和诺伊斯谈话的记录
I have a transcript of that conversation you had with Noyce yesterday.
关于你和雷德斯　这就是关于那些的一切
This is about you and Laeddis. That's all it's ever been about
这上面写的是关于　我和雷德斯
No. No. He is saying that it's about "me and Laeddis".
你问他 他的脸怎么了的时候
When you've asked him what happened to his face,
说　指出来给你看 他说，你做的
said, and I quote again, "You did this".
-他的意思是这是我的错　 -你差点杀了他
- No. He meant it was my fault he... - You almost killed him.
典狱长和这监狱的管理委员会已经做了决定
The warden and the board of overseers are determined something be done. It's been decided.
除非我们能让你变回正常
That unless, we can bring you back  to sanity now, right now,
他们将要采取永久性道德措施 保证你不会再伤害任何人
permanent measures will be taken to ensure you can't hurt anyone ever again.
他们要弄死你　安德鲁
They'll lobotomize you, Andrew.
你懂吗
Do you understand?
是的　我明白
Yeah, I understand.
我明白　很好
I understand just fine.
如果我没有在这和你玩游戏
If... if I don't play along with your little game here.
纳林医生就会把我变成他的鬼魂了
Dr. Naehring is gonna turn me into one of his ghosts.
我的搭档呢
What about my partner?
你的意思我是美国联邦警察 我一厢情愿的自我反射
You're gonna tell the U.S. marshal's office that he's a defense mechanism?
哈噜 老大
Hello, boss.
这怎么回事？
What the fuck is going on here?
你为他工作
You working for him?
我很抱歉必须有人和你在一起　确保你的安全
I'm sorry. There wasn't any other way. Someone had to stick with you. Keep you safe.
你一直在监视我是吗？
You've been watching me, huh?
监视我一分一秒
Watching me every minute.
你是谁
Who... who are you?
你是谁　告诉我
Who are you? Tell me.
你不认识我吗？ 安德鲁
Don't you recognize me, Andrew?
我是你过去两年的精神科主治医生
I've been you primary psychiatrist for the last two years.
我是莱斯特　希恩
I am Lester Sheehan.
我告诉过你　关于我的妻子
And I told you about my wife ...
我知道　我爬到峭壁上去救你
- I know. - I climbed down a cliff to get you.
我相信你我冒着一切危险跟着你　一切危险
I trusted you. I risked everything  to come in here after you. Everything!
我知道　老大
I know, boss.
我们没时间了　安德鲁
We're running out of time here, Andrew,
我在全体海外委员会面前发誓
I swore before the board of overseers that I could construct
我会建立一个精神病学历史上最基础的角色扮演模型
the most radical, cutting edge role-play
那将会把你恢复正常
ever attempted in psychiatry and it would bring you back.
我想如果我们让你按照你虚构的故事演出来
I thought if we let you play this out
我们就能让你看到这是多么不真实不可思议
we could get you to see how untrue, how impossible it is.
我们已经准备那个地方两天了
You've had to run of the place for two days.
告诉我　纳粹的实验在哪
Tell me, where are the Nazi experiments?
那个穷凶极恶的脑部手术实验
The satanic O.R.'s?
安德鲁　听我说
Andrew, listen to me.
如果我们在你身上付出失败了
If we fail with you
那么我们在这里所努力的一切就会被质疑
then everything we've tried to do here will be discredited.
一切
Everything.
我们脑袋里都面临着战争　安德鲁
We are on the front line of a war here, old boy.
现在　你也将面临它
And right now, it'll come down to you.
别动
Don't move! Don't move!
安德鲁　不要　我叫泰德丹尼尔
- Andrew, no! - My name is Edward Daniels.
我可以从重量知道这是把有子弹的真枪
This one is loaded. I can tell by the weight.
我知道了　那是联邦警察的枪　你确定吗
I see. And that's your firearm marshal? You're sure?
枪管有个缺角痕迹...那天菲利苦斯德克就开这把枪射我
My initials are on the side and there's a dent in the barrel from when Philip Stacks shot at me.
子弹反弹造成的.. 你们不能混乱我的思维
You're not going to fuck with my mind on this one Doc
然后炸开了　因为那是你们能离开岛的唯一途径
Then blast away, because that's the only way you're ever getting off this island.
安德鲁　请不要这样
Andrew, please don't.
我的枪
My gun...
你把我的枪怎么了
What have you done to my Goddamn gun.
那是个玩具　安德鲁
It's a toy, Andrew.
我们在告诉你真相
We're telling you the truth.
你老婆 多洛雷斯疯了　精神沮丧　自杀身亡了
Dolores was insane. Manic-depressive. Suicidal.
你喝多了　在旁边　忘掉人们告诉你的一切
You drank. Stayed away. Ignored what everyone had told you.
你去了她那个湖后面的房子
You moved to that lake house after she, purposely,
故意把你在你公寓纵火
set your city apartment on fire
安德鲁　安德鲁　停下来
Andrew! Andrew! Stop it!
你撒谎
You're lying...
这是你的孩子们
Andrew, your children.
瑟琳娜
Simon...
-亨利　 -我没有孩子
- Henry... - I didn't have any children.
你妻子亲手把他们溺死
Your wife drowned them.
就在湖边的小屋中
At the cabin by the lake.
这里　这个小女孩　你
And here, the little girl, the one you dream of
每晚都梦见的
every night.
我没有女儿
I never had a little.
她一遍一遍的告诉你要救她
The one who tells you over and over that you should have saved her
救他们
Saved them all.
你的女儿
Your daughter...
她叫瑞秋　你要否认她曾经活着吗？
Her name was Rachel. Are you going to deny that she ever lived?
安德鲁　你否认吗？
Andrew, are you?
对不起　宝贝
I'm so sorry, baby...
我告诉过你 不要到这里来的
I told you not to come in here.
我告诉你的
I told you...
现在你会死在这里的
this would be the end of you.
我回来了　我们终于抓到他了
I'm back.
就在俄克拉荷马州
We got him just outside of Oklahoma. Must of stopped ten places
追他我至少跑了十个地方　 我可以睡上一整个礼拜
in between here and Tulsa. I could sleep for a week.
多洛雷斯
Dolores?
亲爱的
Baby...
你怎么浑身都是湿透了？
Why are you all wet?
我好想你
I missed you.
我想回家
I want to go home.
你就在家呀
You are home!
孩子们呢
Where are the kids?
在学校呢
They're in school.
今天星期六　亲爱的
It's Saturday, honey.
星期六不上学的
School's not in on Saturday.
我的学校是要上课的
My school is.
哦　天啊
Oh my God!
天
My God!
上帝
God!
哦　上帝　不要
Oh my God, no!
醒过来　醒过来
Come on! Come on!
求求你　上帝　不要
Please, God, no.
不
No!
把他们放厨房桌上吧
Let's put them in the room.
烘干他们
We'll dry them off...
帮他们换件衣服
We'll change their clothes...
他们就是我们活的玩偶了
They'll be our living dolls.
明天我们带他们去野餐
Tomorrow we can take them on a picnic.
如果你爱过我　多洛雷斯
If you ever loved me, Dolores...
请你别再说了
Please stop talking.
我需要你爱我
I love you.
我需要你让我自由
Set me free!
亲爱的
Honey...
我们去给他们洗澡
We'll give them baths...
我好爱你　多洛雷斯　我爱你　我爱你
- I love you so much, Dolores. - And I love you. I love you.
安德鲁
Andrew...
安德鲁　你听得到我吗？
Andrew, can you hear me?
瑞秋　瑞秋
Rachel! Rachel, Rachel...
瑞秋
Rachel.
瑞秋什么
Rachel who?
瑞秋　雷德斯
Rachel Laeddis...
我的女儿
My daughter.
你怎么会在这
Why are you here?
因为我杀了我的妻子
Because I killed my wife.
你为什么那样作
and why did you do that?
她杀了我们的孩子
Dhe murdered our children.
她告诉我让她自由
And she told me to let her go.
-谁是泰德丹尼尔　 -他不存在
- Who is Teddy Daniels? - He doesn't exist.
-瑞秋索兰多也不存在 -是我捏造的
Neither does Rachel Solando. I made them up.
为什么
Why?
我们要听你的说法
We need to hear you say it.
她第一次自杀失败后
After she tried to kill herself the first time,
多洛雷斯告诉我
Dolores told me she...
她的脑子里
she had an insect...
活着一只虫子
living inside her brain.
她能感受到
She could feel it...
它在她脑中穿梭
clicking across her skull...
拉扯她的神经　却只是为了好玩
pulling the wires, just for fun.
她告诉我的
She told me that.
她告诉我　但我没听
She told me but I didn't listen.
我太爱她了
I loved her so much.
为什么你要编造那些
Why did you make them up?
因为我无法相信多洛雷斯杀了我们的孩子
Because I can't take knowing that Dolores killed our children.
我是杀了他们的凶手　因为我都没有帮过她
I killed them, because I didn't get her help.
是我杀了他们
I killed them...
安德鲁　我的理论是.. 我们先前曾有重大突破
Here's my theory, Andrew. We broke through once before,
但九个月前,你又开始退化了
nine months ago, and then you regressed.
-我记不得了　 -我知道
- I don't remember that. - I know.
你重开机(Reset)了　安德鲁　就像录音带
You reset, Andrew. Like a tape playing
不停的一遍一遍播
over and over on an endless loop.
我希望我们做的一切 能够阻止这样的事情再发生了
I hope that what we've done will be enough to stop it from ever happening again
我需要知道
But I need to know ...
你已经接受了现实
you have accepted reality.
你一直紧跟着我　医生
You came after me, huh, doctor?
你一直试着帮我 在大家都束手无策的时候
You tried to help me when no one else would.
我的名字是安德鲁雷德斯
My name is Andrew Laeddis...
我在1952年的春天杀了我的妻子
And I murdered my wife in the spring of '52.
今早上怎么样
How we doing this morning?
还不错,你呢
Good. And You?
没什好抱怨的
Can't complain.
下一步准备干吗?
So what's our next move?
你告诉我
You tell me.
我们要离开这监狱　查克
I've gotta get off this rock, Chuck.
回到陆地上去　这里发生的一切都太糟了
Get back to the mainland. Whatever the hell is going on here. It's bad.
别担心伙伴 我会赶上
Don't worry, partner. They're not gonna catch us.
没错，你看来比他们聪明多了
That's right. We're too smart for them.
是的　我们是啊。
Yeah, we are. Aren't we?
你知道吗　这里让我搞不懂一件事
You know this place makes me wonder.
恩　你指什么　老大
Yeah? What's that boss?
哪种情况最糟
Which would be worse?
你想当一个活着的怪物
To live as a monster ...
还是做一个死去的好人？？
or to die as a good man.
泰德?
Teddy?
感谢观赏
End